There is something wrong with me.
An emptiness.
I thought it started when my sister died,
but now it feels like something bigger.
Just a… void.
Or maybe I'm just bored.
Boo.
They send me a job,
I clock in, clock out, you know?
I'm in the cleanup business.
This week Malaysia, next week, who knows.
I thought throwing myself
into work was the answer.
But I'm not focused, and I'm not happy,
and I don't have purpose.
And without purpose,
I'm just drifting like a river…
or like an old leaf.
Or like an old leaf in a river.
Which do you think is bet-- 'Ey!
You weren't listening to me.
It's like your mind is somewhere else.
Well, whatever.
You're useless to me unless you can get me
past that facial recognition thingy.
Hello.
Can you help me get in there?
No?
You've got your own problems, I guess.
Well, it didn't say how to destroy
the evidence in the assignment.
It's gonna get messy.
Stop right there!
Hi.
Now, that's a face
that can open a scanner.
Did Valentina send you?
This research is property of OXE Group.
-You're gonna tell me I don't understand.
-You don't understand.
-We've made a breakthrough.
-And how you've made a breakthrough.
-And how it's going to change the world.
-No, no, no.
-It could end the world.
-Blah, blah, blah.
Valentina doesn't
understand what happened here.
Look, blame the US government
for their pesky investigation.
Now we have to get rid of all this stuff.
Do you think I like taking orders?
Going from job to job doing
the same thing all the time?
Don't do it. I wouldn't do that.
Always a struggle for a gun.
Oh, God.
You shoot, I dodge.
Oh, my God.
Tell Valentina she's making a mistake.
You guys can never aim for shit.
Always collateral damage.
You try to say your last words.
Project Sentry isn't what she thinks.
But you start to fall asleep.
Oh, damn.
I needed that face.
Okay.
The assignment is-- Oh, wait. Hang on.
Assignment is complete.
What's next?
Representative Barnes,
as a freshman congressman,
any words on today's hearing?
Well, I'm not
on the impeachment committee,
but the rumors of wrongdoing
are very worrying.
They are very, very concerning
and worrying.
And I think that
my Brooklyn constituents deserve better,
so we're gonna get to the bottom
of this worrying issue.
Thank you.
Now, today, the committee is meeting to
examine this official who sits before you.
Articles of impeachment
have been brought against her.
And when we vote
in favor of the impeachment,
she will be removed
from her post permanently.
Please state your name for the record.
Valentina Allegra de Fontaine.
-Miss Fontaine--
-No.
It's "de Fontaine." You forgot the "de."
Mr. Anderson, for example,
is Secretary of Defense,
not secretary of "fense."
Miss de Fontaine.
At this moment, you are serving
as a director of the CIA, correct?
That is correct.
And before that, you were the chairwoman
of the board of OXE Group?
Yes. Although, I have fully
divested in OXE since taking office.
I now sit on the board
in a strategic guidance capacity.
And following this strategic guidance,
the OXE Group
maintains significant holdings
in unregulated labs in foreign countries
and rumored human experimentation.
All part of an illegal operation
to develop your own super… person.
May I speak now, Congressman?
Yes.
First of all, I don't have time to
entertain these rumors and this gossip.
Right now,
there are multiple rogue nations
with technologies that far exceed our own.
And you'll recall
that our last president turned into
a bright red superhuman monster
who nearly destroyed this city.
The Avengers are not
walking through that door.
We have no reliable heroes.
That is why the onus is on me,
on us, the American government,
to shield its citizens. And you know…
Madame Director.
…anything I have done in my roles,
both at OXE or at the CIA,
has been done with that goal in mind.
Order. Madame Director.
I officially reject
these articles of impeachment.
This is a partisan waste of time.
And your hunt will come up empty,
no matter how many nooks and crannies
you happen to stick your nose in.
So you don't mind if this committee
continues this investigation?
Of course not.
Shit.
We gotta get all of this outta here ASAP.
Yep. So far they've removed
all the case studies…
Okay, just get rid of any hanging chads
that could get me impeached
or land me in federal prison.
Copy. No prison.
What about our shadow ops
out in the field?
Did all those loose ends get tied up?
Well, the ends are tied,
yes, but the rope is on fire.
What?
Can you please just say it normal?
Okay, one operative blew up an entire
laboratory in the middle of Kuala Lumpur.
Whatever.
Did the new assignments get sent out?
Yes, ma'am. All but one have checked in.
Where is she?
There's Brezhnev.
Those guys with the little waves.
Get out of my way.
Get out of my--
I click "leave on porch."
Your "subordinance"
will be reported to DoorDash HQ.
Alexei, it's me. Open up.
Yelena?
Hold on!
"Protecting you from boring evening."
Yelena! So good to see you.
Hi, Dad.
Sorry for the wait.
I was on important call.
Highly classified.
How long has it been, huh? A year?
Wow, yeah, I guess-- I guess it has been.
You've been busy with work?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, a lot of… a lot of work.
-Me too.
-Too many irons in the fire.
Security.
My limo business.
You would not believe
the important people I meet driving.
So you… you feel fulfilled?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, so full, so filled.
Move to DC, best decision I ever made.
Isn't this technically Baltimore?
No. Baltimore start next block over.
But why do you ask this?
What-- What brings you here?
I-- I wanted to talk
to you about Valentina.
Okay. New assignment.
You come to Red Guardian.
You want a little help.
No, I-- I think I'm gonna quit.
What?
I would burn the city
to the ground to work for her.
What? You just said you were fulfilled.
Lena, I was lying.
Look around you. I'm miserable.
Give me her number.
-No way. Alexei, stop, stop.
-Give to me. I call her. I use--
Lena!
Lena, what is wrong?
The light inside you is dim
even by Eastern European standards.
I've just been wondering, you know,
like, what… is the point?
In any of this?
The point of work is fame and fortune.
Fortune buys friends,
and love, and a lot of cool clothes.
-Okay. Thank you.
-Okay, okay--
-No, never mind. It's fine.
-No, no, no. Okay.
You want to know when I was really happy?
Yes, please.
When I was serving my country as a hero.
Saving civilians in the streets.
Being cheered on by the crowd.
Adored like a god.
There is no higher calling.
Your sister understood
something about that.
Perhaps it is time
that you followed in her path.
Why do you have this photo out?
We were so bad.
You were happy.
I'll make you something.
You know,
I'm still super soldier in his prime.
Maybe you could put in a good word
with Valentina for me, huh?
Okay, Val. Reporting for duty.
What's my next assignment?
Thank you, Ms. Belova.
I was starting to worry.
After this though, I-- I need a change.
Oh, really?
Yeah, maybe something more public facing.
Interesting.
Yelena's ready for her close-up?
Yeah, this just
isn't working for me anymore.
Okay, well,
you know I love promoting women.
You complete this last assignment for OXE,
and you have a deal.
Okay?
Okay.
There's a warehouse facility, a vault,
built a mile down into a mountain.
It stores all of
OXE Group's most sensitive assets.
Intel's come in that a rogue operative
with attributes
perfectly tailored to rob me
is intending to… well, rob me.
I need you to follow the target inside
and find out what she intends to steal.
I'll add your biometrics to the system.
You'll have full access.
Once you assess what's being stolen,
you have the go-ahead
to terminate on sight.
And then, no problem.
You know,
we can find you some "good guy" material.
It's simple, really.
It's just one little target…
and you're done.
What is happening?
You're not even my target.
You're mine.
I'm not here for you.
There you are.
Now what?
Oh, get over yourself.
Stay out of my way.
Oh, God.
Is she actually dead?
No. Hi. Hey.
I'm-- I'm Bob.
Yes, these are the Chitauri handcuffs.
Recovered from the Battle of New York
by the first responders.
They came with the new property.
Just reminds us that, of course,
we struggle, but then we get back up.
-Yes, we do.
-I love it. Yeah.
That's inspiring.
Thank you, Congressman.
I'm so happy that you're here.
Yes, this is a beautiful fake event, Val.
"The First Responders Family Fund."
-Yes.
-That's cute.
Cute?
This won't sway the votes
enough to save your ass.
Okay. So, can you go get him, Mel?
-Yep.
-Thank you.
This gaudy Avenger propaganda
reeks of desperation.
If you really thought that,
you wouldn't be here.
You're scared because your investigation
of my office came up clean.
Squeaky clean.
Almost like someone had frantically
gotten rid of all the evidence.
Or like someone was incredibly innocent.
Without proof, this impeachment thing
is running on borrowed time.
-Excuse me, Congressman.
-Turn around.
-How great.
-Thank you.
-Thank you so much.
-Thank you very much.
What do you think?
-Hi.
-Mel, right?
This must all seem like
ancient history to you.
You know, Kierkegaard says that
life can only be understood backwards.
-Very true.
-Is it?
I don't know, actually.
It did sound good, though.
He did believe that it was up
to individuals to create values.
I know who you are and what you're doing.
What am I doing?
You're working me.
You're trying to get me on your side.
Okay, look. I…
You say you know who I am.
So you know my story, and you know
I didn't have a choice who I worked for.
But you do.
I need to keep Valentina on schedule.
What is this? This your trash?
It's my business card.
In case you need some help or,
you know, you wanna share
some secret hidden evidence.
Okay. Goodbye.
Who are you?
I'm-- I'm Bob. I told you. I'm…
Yeah. Bob.
Jesus Christ. Stop saying "Bob."
-Who sent you, Bob?
-Nobody.
Why would I be sent?
Were you all-- You were all sent?
Okay, I'm not sure what's happening here,
but you're all exhausting
and my job is done, so--
But you see my job
is to keep an eye on you.
So, no, you are not gonna go
anywhere anymore.
So you're keeping an eye on her, huh?
That's a halfway decent cover
for somebody stealing assets from OXE.
I'm not stealing. She's stealing.
Okay.
It's clear
we have all worked for Valentina
in some sort of shadow ops capacity.
Yeah. So?
So all of this stuff is OXE's secrets.
But so are we.
Which makes us liabilities
that no one would miss.
Speak for yourself.
We are the evidence,
and this is the shredder.
She wants us gone.
Your theory's flawed.
Oh, please. Go on.
Okay. Well, look at the facts.
The infamous Ghost.
A SHIELD reject on the run
from 15 nations?
The dead one over there,
she destroyed half of Budapest.
-Don't talk about her like that.
-And you, former Red Room assassin.
God only knows the blood on your hands.
Pretty ludicrous coming from
the dime-store Captain America.
I'll have you know I was actually
the official Captain America, so…
Yeah, for, like, two seconds.
Before you publicly murdered
an innocent man on the streets.
-Do I have that right?
-Really? Define "innocent."
Hey, look.
I'm a decorated combat veteran, okay?
I have a loving wife and a son.
Let's be honest,
you guys are just cheap mercenaries. Okay?
So, I--
Clearly, I'm supposed to bring you in.
That was funny. Thank you. We needed that.
It was getting so tense in here
for a second.
I'm not leaving here
without completing my mission.
Valentina gave me a clean slate guarantee,
and I'm not screwing that up.
But this weirdo wasn't part of the job,
so I gotta know…
How'd you get in?
I don't-- I don't remember.
Terrific answer.
All right. Tie yourselves up.
-Wow. No.
-Oh, my God.
And goodbye.
You guys hear that?
Isn't that amazing? Cheers.
And she said, "Not on my watch."
-Congressman Gary.
-Hey!
I have a plan.
Holy shit, Bucky.
The assistant, she's ductile.
-Ductile?
-Yeah.
I mean, good. But next time, why don't you
just text me like a normal person?
Look, we're safe here.
We're in a blind spot, okay?
Away from those two cameras.
Just hold on, all right?
We don't need to go rogue in the darkness,
or whatever you people do.
Hold on? You don't know
what Val is capable of.
We need to move fast,
and the assistant is on the fence.
Without a smoking gun, the best chance to
get Val out of power is to whip the votes.
And you can help with that
and then let the system do its job.
The system that goes on recess
every day at 4:00 p.m.
We are in a good spot, I assure you.
My team is putting together
a juicy packet for the next hearing.
-Packet?
-Yes, Bucky.
Read the packets.
Is it time?
I can confirm all your "guests"
are in attendance,
and vault level five
has been completely sealed off.
All right, then.
"All right, then.
Move on to the final step"? Or…
Torch it all.
Right.
-Are you-- Are you sure?
-Oh, my God.
Hey.
Job or not, can you have
some respect, please?
Yeah, Jesus.
Hold on a second.
What? She'd want me to have it.
I need it.
What the hell is that?
That doesn't sound like a shredder.
It's an incinerator.
Two minutes.
Then Valentina's slate is wiped clean.
You don't know that for sure.
Could be for anything.
Could be for when they come to pick me up.
Do you feel that?
The temperature rising dramatically
as if heat was involved?
Okay, it's an incinerator.
Oh, boy. That is no way to go.
Well, how would you
like to die today, Bob?
Okay, ghost lady.
-Ava.
-Sure. Whatever. Don't care.
We need to get you through the walls,
so that you can open the door.
She tried that already.
I know she did. But we haven't tried
shutting down the sound barrier.
Well, if they built it just for her,
there's gotta be
an independent power source.
Come on. Let's go.
What-- What exactly are we looking for?
We're looking for
not-stupid questions, Bob.
I think I found it.
Move!
Okay, I can override this.
On your left!
Or that works, I hope.
Go, go, go.
You think she's coming back?
I should have seen this coming.
Yelena!
Yelena, c'mon!
What?
Lunch will be over soon.
Why'd you bring us so far out?
Anya, over here!
No.
I'm sorry.
Well done, Yelena.
Your first test is now complete.
You okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Hey. Didn't think you'd come back. Thanks.
I had to.
Someone cut the power to the elevator.
Lovely evening.
Nice to be in the room, you know?
Okay. What is it, Mel?
Just spit it out already. What?
It's your "guests."
They've somehow evaded
the "housewarming gift."
-Come on.
-And…
God, is it possible that
they've maybe joined forces against you?
Mel. These are defective losers.
Antisocial tragedy in human form.
You know, honestly, I cannot think
of a worse group of people
trying to work together.
-My god.
-Right.
It's just that--
-What?
-They're working together.
What--
Who the hell is this guy?
I have no idea.
I need an ID on John Doe.
I wanna know how this man-boy got into
my supposedly impenetrable stronghold.
-Copy.
-And call Holt.
Give him the vault coordinates.
I want the full strike team mobilized.
-We need to end this now.
-Okay.
Calling now.
Holt? It's Mel. Ready for coordinates?
I was trying to help…
Everybody's got a reason
for being here except this guy.
Hey, Bobby.
Less talking to yourself,
more talking to us.
-I'm tired of this bullshit.
-Hey, Walker.
You tell me how you got in here
right goddamn now.
I swear, man,
I just woke up in this place.
One minute, I was, you know,
getting my blood drawn
for this medical study,
and the next I'm here.
In my pajamas.
I don't know what's happening.
Okay, then show me where you woke up.
In-- In there.
Where everything's on fire.
That's real convenient.
Walker, relax.
You don't remember anything?
Bag over your head?
-A needle in your neck?
-No.
-Choke hold? Nerve pinch?
I think he's just a civilian.
If he's a civilian, he knows too much.
If he's an agent, he sucks.
Either way I say
we throw him back into the fire.
Sorry. Look--
You said you were Captain America?
Why are you laughing?
Just 'cause you're an asshole.
You know?
It's just funny. I mean…
Hey. Okay. Okay!
We swung our tiny dicks.
It was a lot of fun.
You go over there.
Bob, come with me.
Come here.
-Are you hurt?
-No, I'm fine. I'm fine.
You do not seem fine.
Yeah, well, we've only just met.
This is…
This is how I am.
The talking to yourself?
Yeah.
-The emo aggressive thing?
-I mean--
That-- That guy's
been a dick to me from the start.
I get it. He sucks.
But we have to work together
to get out of here, so…
Well, you guys should just go without me.
It'll be easier.
No, you'll die down here.
Yeah. Well, whatever. I mean…
I think everyone's better off
if I just stay put.
Okay, I-- I-- I understand.
We all feel like shit sometimes.
And loneliness, I get that. I get it.
And that--
that darkness gets pretty enticing.
And then it starts to feel
a little bit like…
A void.
Yep. A void.
What do you do about it?
You shove it way down.
You just… push it down.
That's great-- That's really good advice.
You're welcome.
You guys done with therapy yet?
I think I found a way out.
Look, we're all alone.
All of us.
Let's just stick together
until we make it to the surface,
and after that, you can start a fight
with a super soldier.
Get yourself killed. I don't care. Okay?
Okay. Yeah.
"If the resolution of impeachment
is adopted."
Stupid packets.
Oh, God. Boring.
Hello?
Hi. This is Mel.
Mel. Hi.
-You called.
-I did.
I know that you're new to DC,
and I wanted to network.
Network?
So, how are you feeling
about your new job?
It's great. Love it.
It's not ancient history, you know.
I was in high school when the aliens came.
And the Avengers.
High school, huh?
I was, like, 90.
It's kinda strange
that it's all over now, right?
I mean, Avengers are gone.
No one else is coming to save the day.
Maybe we could be the people
that are coming.
Just come in and testify against her.
You must really not know my boss.
We can protect you.
Can you?
Is that coming from
the freshman congressman
who hasn't gotten a bill passed
or the Winter Soldier?
Come on, Mel. Just give me something.
Hey-- You can track my phone, right?
Yes, I can, but I don't do that anymore.
Thank you, Congressman.
Have a great night.
So,
none of us fly?
What, do we all just punch and shoot?
Okay. Don't worry. I got this.
You should try that again.
We're pretty far down here.
Hey. Okay, why don't you walk up
through the walls or whatever
and then just throw us a rope down?
-Yeah.
-That's...
Okay, well, first of all, someone
other than you would have to ask me.
And second of all,
I'd have to know where I'm going
'cause I've never been able
to hold it longer than a minute.
So I'd just get lost in an ocean of dirt,
and then I'd be crushed to death.
-All right?
-Just a minute?
-Oh, shut up.
-Oh, my God. We suck.
I have an idea.
Right.
Left.
Which one of you is wet?
I run hot. Sorry.
-Someone's got a weird, hard butt.
-That's not my butt. It's my suit.
Well, you need to get a new suit.
Pardon me for the inconvenience.
I mean, I only spent my entire life
in labs hooked up to machines
so I could create this physical cage
to keep my material body
from disintegrating at all times.
So, yeah, I'm so sorry about that.
You do not want to start
the whole sob story game.
I win.
Enslaved child assassin over here.
Well, you were just a kid, so...
So that's a good thing now?
I just think it might be nice to know
that you didn't really know any better.
Thanks. I feel way better.
Hey, quit it.
-Okay. Okay.
-Ready?
Right. Oh, God.
Oh, my God. Why are you gasping?
Please don't gasp at work.
It's the John Doe.
He's Sentry Project.
No, everyone who went through
Sentry Project is dead, Mel.
That's why we're in
this whole stupid mess.
Yeah, but look. There.
Robert Reynolds entered
the pre-trial program in Malaysia,
and he'd had a real rough go before that.
One of the test subjects.
How did he get in my vault?
He was supposed to be dead.
You threw him out
with the rest of the evidence.
If he survived the procedure,
that means...
Yeah. It might actually work.
Oh, my God.
It's crazy. I can't even see the floor.
Can we not talk about how high up we are?
I'm just not great with heights.
Hey, I think I see the door.
-Yeah. Yeah.
-Okay. Okay.
Now what?
I guess one of us should go...
first.
Then the other three immediately fall.
Shit.
Sorry. Yeah, I guess I didn't...
I didn't really think this far ahead.
Genius plan, Bobby.
Always making things worse.
These bloody boots.
I don't think I can hold this much longer.
Okay. Hand me your baton.
-I can reach it.
-What?
-Yeah.
-No way. You're just going to leave us.
Okay.
Spin us around, and then I can...
I can latch us on.
I'm not spinning us around, okay?
Somebody's got to go first.
Cucumber, cucumber, cucumber.
What the hell is happening?
Growing up, somebody told me that you can
stop a sneeze if you confuse your brain.
-I always just yelled "cucumber."
-Okay.
I have to sneeze. But if I sneeze,
then I'm going to lose control.
This is insane, okay?
I can get us all out of here.
-I just need to go first.
-No. There's got to be another way.
Oh, no.
-Cucumber! Cucumber!
All right! Come on!
Okay, just give me this. I got it!
You selfish prick.
Yet, you're all safe.
I made a tactical decision to secure
my own safety and ensure all yours.
Pretty ungrateful if you ask me, but...
You gonna make it, Bobby?
Looks like you might have missed
arm, leg and chest day.
-John?
-What?
Are you watching him?
What? I'm doing it. I'm watching him.
-John.
-What, Olivia? What?
-Please.
-I'm watching him. He's fine.
You're in your phone.
Look, you don't like the way that I do it,
then you can do it yourself, okay?
It's okay. It's okay.
Walker.
What the hell are you doing?
I'm fine.
All right, let's get out of here.
-Okay, we need to come up with a plan.
-Here's what we're gonna do.
You're the boss now? Cute.
Well, yeah, it's our only chance
of getting out of here, so...
Okay, I think I might
just surrender, probably.
Okay, fine. Every man for himself.
Why should you be in charge?
You almost killed all of us right there.
Well, let's see. I've been in the trenches
of every war-torn country on this planet,
rescued God knows how many hostages
and shook the hands of two US presidents.
What else?
High school state football champs
back-to-back-to-back. Go Bears.
Wow. When I was five,
I was in a peewee soccer team called
the West Chesapeake Valley Thunderbolts
sponsored by Shane's Tire Shop.
We won zero games,
and one time, this girl, Mindy,
she did a poo at midfield.
Anyone else have any
pointless childhood stories to tell?
Grew up in a lab prison.
Meth-addicted sign-twirling chicken.
It was a summer job.
Right. Okay, here's the plan.
-We set off an explosion to bring them in.
-No. Too many variables with an explosion.
They turn on their night vision.
You handle the first wave,
but you wait for me
after I've blinded the remaining troops.
-So I'm just going to wait for ya?
-It will only work if you wait.
-Terrible plan.
-Ava, you find an escape vehicle.
What about me?
You stay behind me, Bob.
Let's do this.
What's the latest?
We're dug in, ma'am.
Got it covered from all angles.
There's no way out.
Breach team ready at the front.
It's going to be non-lethal protocol.
Non-lethal?
No one told me this was non-lethal.
Well, I'm telling you now, Holt.
It's just...
I've spent a lot
of time planning for lethal.
Then change the plan. Okay?
There's somebody inside there
I don't want catching any strays.
Get down!
Strike Team 4, enter now.
Non-lethal.
In one minute, these all go back on.
Okay.
Maybe I should have a gun?
No, I don't think so.
We're gonna need to fight, right? So...
I will fight. You stay behind me.
You know, the medical trial
was supposed to make me better,
and, I don't know,
I feel like maybe I could help.
I thought you said
that you didn't know anything about it.
No, not much. I just remember
they said it was for people
who wanted to make
something better of themselves.
You can trust me, Bob.
Can I?
No, not really.
I've always had these episodes
since I was a kid.
There's a... There's a high,
then there's a big low,
and then my memory just goes blank.
But this time, I feel like there's...
I don't know, something bad happened
or I did something bad.
I mean, everyone here has done bad things.
I think this was like
a whole new kind of--
Lights up.
No. Why... Why did that not work?
Well, you got to turn the power back on.
I mean, you got to blind the guys.
Yeah, I know that, Bob.
-That was your plan.
-You're not being helpful, Bob.
Give me that. Follow me.
I hate to say it,
but I think Walter was right on this one.
His name is Walker, Bob.
Turn on the lights, Yelena.
I got to do everything myself.
I will repeat,
Tango Foxtrot Lima requesting report.
Next team up, get in there!
-Where is he?
-He's gone.
Every man for himself, right?
Shit.
Get down!
-I can help.
-Stay behind me.
Bob, stay!
That's it. You're done.
No, wait! I can help!
-Take this!
-Yes! How do I use it?
You point and shoot.
Shit.
-Sorry!
-A little higher!
-That was awesome.
-Not at me!
No! Stop! Stop shooting!
Stop! Stop! It's me! It's John! Stop!
-Where were you?
The explosion fried the wires.
I told you, too many variables. I knew it.
-And then, you didn't wait.
-I did wait!
What's going on in there?
Do we need to go lethal?
Okay.
We probably got about 60 seconds
until they mobilize.
And if ghost lady actually did
what she was supposed to,
maybe we'll all get out of here alive.
I don't really want to be carried anymore.
Shut up, Bob. You're injured, remember?
We need a truck.
Where's Ava?
She's gone. Of course she's gone.
Now what?
Hey! Get in.
You going to be okay back here?
-Yeah. All good.
-Yeah? Okay.
Second time you came back.
This was the only way out, okay?
-That's all.
-All right.
Oh, shit.
All right.
Just let me do the talking, okay?
-Oh, my God.
-Here we go.
Identify yourself, soldiers.
Part of the medical team.
Need to get the wounded to the hospital.
Medical bay's set up north side.
Nah, medical bay won't suffice.
We were headed off-base.
No one leaves the premises
until mission is completed.
Orders are no deviations from protocol.
Identify yourself.
-No.
-Wow, masterful.
Remove your helmets and identify yourself.
-Now, soldiers!
-You are messing with the wrong--
Hey!
Over here!
Move, move, move!
Oh, no. Bob helped.
Open fire. End this now.
I want him toes up.
-What the hell are you doing?
-This has gone far--
Cease fire! Cease fire!
Cease fire!
Come on. Let's go.
Come on. Let's go. That's why he did it.
What the...
Is that...
Mel, I need you
to connect me to our satellites.
I need to know exactly where he's going,
and I need it now.
I... I think he's coming back down.
-No. No, no, no.
-Oh, shit.
Oh, God.
I'll call an Uber.
Jesus Christ.
I know. What was that?
That was her.
She did that to him.
Well, she turned him
into a tomahawk cruise missile.
You were right,
she definitely wants us dead.
To test on someone like that,
it's inhuman.
Yeah, she's lost it.
Nope. She's found it.
And she'll use it.
What is this?
"Power of a thousand exploding suns."
"Golden Guardian of Good."
That's a mouthful.
Wow.
Sentry.
Very shiny, I'll give them that.
What do you know about this?
There was a rumor
that OXE was on the verge
of some kind of big breakthrough.
Whatever it was was way too extreme.
Test subjects were dying.
When the government looked into it,
Val shut it down.
She put me on cleanup duty.
Let's just make it home
without getting cratered.
Might need new homes.
Anybody hungry?
Cactus berry.
Let me see here.
So, that woman back there that I...
You knew her?
Yeah, I did.
She had a tough life.
She killed a lot of people,
and then she got killed.
Same as us someday.
It's a shit life.
Yeah, well...
what other life can we have?
Says the guy with the Norman Rockwell
family waiting for him at home.
Yeah.
How do you do it?
Well, you just keep working
at it every day.
Never give up.
Beautiful.
Dr. Phil, that was really beautiful.
Yeah. You know that show's
not on anymore, right?
Yeah, it is. I watch it.
Nah, it got canceled a few years ago.
It was a good show while it was on,
but it's not on anymore.
Gotta be like a YouTube thing.
They took him off cable.
Well, it isn't great.
Seven local outlets
have picked up the story of the blast.
One has already connected
the vault to OXE.
And I have 15 messages
from concerned House members
on our side of the aisle.
You know, I don't say it enough,
but I am so impressed
that in circumstances like this,
you can still get me a good cup of coffee.
It's extraordinary.
Thank you.
Okay, time to pivot.
I'm gonna need a new team of scientists.
And I want them there when we arrive.
Okay, DC?
No. The new place.
But we stopped mid-renovation.
When we shut down the project.
Exactly. We're officially un-shut down.
What about Yelena and the others?
Nothing yet.
Get rid of them, Mel.
They're the last piece of evidence.
On it.
Let me know when our boy
in the box gets to New York.
Those birds are way too high.
They're doing recon loops at 4,000 feet.
I mean, they don't know
what they're doing.
They'll be five or ten clicks away
in no time.
All right, Walker, we get it.
You were in the military.
Five or ten clicks to the bird.
There.
It's a... I don't... What is that?
Oh, no.
What?
It's coming right at us.
-Who is that?
-It's no one.
It's nothing.
-Oh, God.
-Yelena!
It's your dad!
Don't go in the vault!
Valentina's gonna burn you alive!
Yelena!
So, I finagled to pick up
Miss de Fontaine at fancy event.
I figure good networking,
but as soon as I overhear
the coordinates of the vault,
I rush home, I get the tactical beast.
And then, I drive straight here.
America's so big.
You ever drive through Oklahoma?
It's so flat.
I forgot to tell you,
don't drink from the Big Gulp back there.
Alexei, have you slept?
I'll sleep when I'm dead!
I'd like not to die today.
So maybe somebody else should be driving.
Mr. Walker,
second coming of Captain America.
You and I have a lot in common, you know?
I too was state-sponsored
super soldier in Russia.
But also very different because
Walker actually knows what he's doing.
And Ghost. What a magician.
You disappear. You reappear.
When you reappear, does sometimes
things not pop up in right place?
I find it best
just to ignore him sometimes.
What impressive friends
you've assembled, Yelena.
We are not friends, Alexei.
Nah. We're just disposable delinquents.
Whatever you are,
the light inside you is brighter, Yelena.
How about this?
You are a team of scrappy antiheroes.
-Yeah. Go Thunderbolts.
-What?
-Yelena...
-Oh, my God.
You named them
after your peewee soccer club?
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
The West Chesapeake Valley Thunderbolts.
Sponsored by Dmitri's Elite
Industrial Lighting and Electronics.
No, no. No.
Never won a game,
but Yelena had so much fun.
-There was a girl who pooped in one game.
-No. It was-- It was not--
It was crazy. I was yelling at the ref.
It was sponsored by Shane's Tire Shop.
-Shane?
-Yes.
What's this talk of Shane?
-It was.
-He didn't have that kind of money.
-Yes, it was.
-No! Shane? What a joke.
You really need to sleep.
Okay. What about this Bob you mentioned?
What's the plan? Where am I driving?
It's not like that.
We need to escape and we need to hide.
Yeah, way smarter for us to split up.
There's actually
an airfield not far from here.
-We'll just disappear from there.
-Split up? No, no, no.
You may not see what I see,
but I have been around long time.
No shit.
This has the makings of a team
that can raise to glory.
A team that can bring light
from the darkness.
A team of heroes that can be
on the Wheaties box
-and have little kiddie toy...
-No, no.
This is not a marketing opportunity, okay?
Valentina is hunting us,
and we cannot win.
Do you understand?
-You don't understand.
-I do. You don't.
Look, you say that Valentina
is going to use the power
-of this Sentry Project...
-Yes. Yes.
...to take over and kill us all.
-Yes.
-Well, you need to stand up to her.
You and your team.
You got a convoy approaching fast.
-Step on it.
-Aye, aye, Captain.
Is that it?
-Okay, any time now.
-Yeah, yeah, yeah. We're working on it.
-A little bit faster.
-It takes a second.
Alexei!
-Alexei!
-Okay! Don't worry!
Don't worry. She's bulletproof, huh?
Engaging defensive measures.
What the hell?
Oh, my God.
Wait, that's not supposed to do that.
Come on.
Who are you driving?
Walker, shield!
What happened to "bulletproof"?
-Bulletproof-ish.
-Jesus Christ!
God, everyone's a critic today!
Time to break out the bottle service.
Come on, Ghost, give me the good stuff.
Okay, not really appropriate.
Vodka! Vodka, now!
Oh, my God. This is so not the time.
What's wrong with you?
Oh, no, no, no!
Give me a break.
No.
Okay, I'll be back. I hope.
Yelena! What are you doing?
There's nothing you can do.
What?
It's Bucky!
The Winter Soldier.
That's what I talk about!
Yes! Yeah!
Oh, sh--
Congressman!
Why did you call an emergency session
of the impeachment committee?
What I can say is that I've gotten
a tip from a trusted cohort
that will be bringing some new
evidence in, and that evidence is juicy.
The impeachment was just an appetizer.
They should be getting a nice, cozy cell
in federal prison ready for Miss Fontaine.
I just got word the impeachment committee
is convening tonight.
This is serious, Val.
Were you able to get the lab
fully operational?
Yes, but the rest of the building
is only 70 percent finished.
Okay, Mel. We'll get it there.
Welcome to The Watchtower.
Val, something happened in Malaysia.
Have you read his file?
Delusions of grandeur, depression.
I mean, someone that imbalanced
amplified by the treatment...
The people in the labs,
they were just test subjects.
They were never gonna be the one.
Does this look nurturing enough?
Very nurturing.
Hi. How are you feeling, Robert?
Are you comfortable?
Yeah.
My name is Valentina Allegra de Fontaine.
Oh, no, no, no.
You-- You tried to kill us, didn't you?
Let me explain.
Would-- Would you like that?
Yeah.
You signed up
for a medical study which was,
as advertised,
at the cutting edge of human improvement.
But not everybody could handle the amount
of greatness that we had in mind.
What happened to Yelena?
Yelena?
Well, those people you were with,
those are not honest people.
They're criminals. Villains, really.
No, no. They-- They helped me.
Robert. Let's just forget about them,
and let's focus on you.
And how perfect you are.
Perfect, huh?
You always thought of yourself
as a victim.
But you overcame.
You went to Malaysia.
You were lost, right? You were searching.
And you found me.
How-- How do you know all that?
I know all of it.
I know about your mom's mental illness.
I know about your addiction
and your juvenile record.
I mean, I even know
about the times your father--
Stop! No, no, no.
I didn't say you could know that.
Robert, I know everything about you.
And I still want you to be my guy.
And isn't that what you want?
To be accepted? To be chosen?
No one else sees it,
but I do.
And I think maybe your past
is what makes you so perfect.
Stay quiet, Valentina.
Completely quiet, no matter what you hear.
You promise me?
Did I do something wrong?
The man in town asked where we live.
He said he was your friend, so I told him.
Yes, well he was.
Remember I told you not to talk to anyone?
Yes, daddy. I'm so sorry.
It's okay. Just stay hidden for me.
You know...
I've been in this business a long time.
There's always someone like you,
smart, but cocky.
A hungry dog who already had
a bone in his mouth.
Let's have a drink, shall we?
You still think
you're getting away with this.
Don't worry,
I'll look out for your sweet Valentina.
Would you excuse me just for a moment?
No. All right. Wait. Wait. Wait.
I can control it.
Great.
All right, let's get the press here
in the morning.
It's time to show everyone
what I've been working on.
Val, you put a serum into
someone like Steve Rogers,
he becomes Captain America,
but you do it to someone this unstable,
I mean, who knows what it did to him?
That's why we build in safeguards.
Didn't we make a kill switch?
Yeah, but we threw it out
along with everything else.
Well, then remake it.
I don't really care who this guy was.
I do know what he can become.
Get the press here like I asked.
No, no, no, no!
Just when I get my team together.
Mr. Soldier, you are making
terrible mistake.
Save it for the committee.
What committee?
You're all evidence in
the impeachment trial against Valentina.
We don't even work for Valentina anymore.
She tried to kill us.
We were ordered to destroy
all of her secrets,
but really, we were just sent
to kill each other in this vault.
But then we met Bob.
Yeah. Bob.
There was a man in the vault.
She's done something to him.
It's called Project Sentry.
Okay, he shot up into the sky.
He exploded.
And then he crashed into this mountain,
and then he died, didn't die--
Yes, I got it. He's very, very scary.
-So rude.
-Okay.
"Congressman Barnes."
All right, Walker.
What's that supposed to mean?
Means you know me, Bucky.
So cut the shit and listen
to what we're trying to tell you.
Yeah, I know you, John,
and you made your choices.
I know it's been hard
since Olivia left you and took your kid,
but still, this is on you.
Bucky, there won't be
a committee left. Okay?
There might not even be a government.
She has some big--
Threat. Yes. I got it.
Named "Bob" or "Sentry" who flies. Right?
And you're all heroes going after Val,
ready to save the day.
-Am I supposed to believe that?
-We weren't going after her together.
We were just trying
to get home alive, actually.
That's even more pathetic.
Yeah, I know.
That's what I've been telling them.
-Shut up.
-I'm not going to shut up. No.
All right. Plane lands in six minutes.
-Will you be quiet?
-Yes?
Bucky, I need your help.
What is it?
Val has gone off the rails.
I mean, Project Sentry is not
just a failure. It's dangerous.
Project Sentry?
She has too much power in her hands.
And this guy is
a disaster waiting to happen.
-What guy?
-Bob.
Bob?
Bob!
We're at the old Avengers place.
The press are set to come
tomorrow morning.
Someone has to do something.
Shit. Okay, I have to go.
But come now, please.
Bring anyone. Everyone you can.
Bob.
-Bob.
-How many times?
I know.
It's bad, Bucky.
Hang on. What are you doing?
I'm letting you go. You're coming with me.
Why?
For the glory.
Well, you know Valentina.
She's got this thing out there.
People are gonna get hurt,
and I gotta stop her.
And you are gonna help me.
Wait. Us?
Why? You got some place to be?
Bucky, you have the wrong people.
Look, I've been where you are.
You can run, but it doesn't go away.
Sooner or later it catches up to you,
and when it does, it's too late.
So you can either
do something about it now,
or live with it forever.
Stop Val and save Bob.
Fine.
Yeah.
Go on, then.
Yes!
Yeah!
What'd you think this job was gonna be?
I don't know. I hope I've done some good.
"Good."
Good girl. Good enough.
You want to be good?
Or do you want to be somebody
who changes the world?
Can't I be both?
I mean, I thought you wanted
to change the world for the better too.
Mel, righteousness without power
is just an opinion.
Look, you're brought up to believe
that there's a good guy and a bad guy.
But then eventually, you come to realize
that there's a bad guy and a worse guy.
And nothing else.
Let me know when you come to your senses.
I don't know.
-Okay, yeah. We just try again.
-Yeah.
Let's just focus.
I believe in you.
I can do that?
You can do anything.
People think they know you.
They just see you as "Bob."
They pity Bob.
I'm the only one who knows
what your true potential is, Robert.
And it's limitless.
Ready for the next lesson?
And then I have these little,
Widow bite things.
-And in the left...
-Yeah. I remember.
And then I have this 19.
Forty-five. The long barrel.
-Wow. It's big.
-Yeah. Well, it's--
It's long.
-Yeah.
-Yeah, yeah, yeah.
-Okay, it's a little long.
-Yeah. Big gun.
And... what about your hat?
The hat? The helmet?
Yeah. Whatever you want to call it.
It's, like, cool. Right? You like it?
Do you like the hat?
-Yeah, I think the hat's pretty sweet.
-Then, cool.
What kind of super serum did you get?
I don't know. Regular. Hydra.
Hydra?
-Fancy.
-Yes.
Mine was Soviet recreation.
But it's still good, you know?
-We are same. You and me.
-Well...
I mean, we are different, but we are same.
You know, we could be coleaders in this.
Little different.
You get tired, I drive.
I don't get tired.
No, I mean metaphorically.
I don't actually want to drive.
Are we there yet?
-Almost!
Okay. Mr. Soldier,
what is secret plan, huh?
The plan?
Yeah.
Open up on him!
Go, go!
I like this plan.
Jesus, you guys,
I literally just put that drywall in.
I left the door unlocked for you. Come up.
How crazy is it to think
of all the monumental fights
that happened exactly here
where you're standing?
I don't really care.
I mean, the place wasn't cheap,
but it's got good optics.
Well, it's over, Valentina.
This ends today.
Congressman Barnes, wow.
You know, I never really thought
you'd have a promising political career.
But less than half a term?
Yikes.
We're taking you in, Val.
I don't think so.
Junior Varsity Captain America.
Walker.
Nice to see you, Ava.
Yelena. You look awful.
You sure you're really ready for that
public facing role you asked me about?
Eat shit, Valentina. Where's Bob?
Look at you. You are all so adorable.
Just think, I send you down there
to kill each other,
and instead, you make nice
and you form a team.
Who's this old Santa?
I'm Alexei Shostakov.
The Red Guardian.
What?
-Where's Mel?
-Mel?
Mel. Yeah.
Mel is having a little loyalty issue.
But I'm just so grateful that she stayed
long enough to lure you all in.
I'm not alone.
Robert?
Oh, my God.
That's Bob?
Yeah, he's changed a little.
It is my great honor
to introduce to you The Sentry.
Hey, guys.
Wow. That's cool name.
All-powerful. Invincible.
Stronger than all of the Avengers
rolled into one.
And soon to be known
as Earth's mightiest hero.
Have you dyed your hair?
Yeah. Well, it was...
Yeah, it was my idea.
People love a classic hero.
Okay, I'll bite. What's the plan?
You haven't figured it out yet, Bucky?
Geez.
Well, at least you're kind of cute.
You're not going to hurt people.
Oh, no.
No, I'm not gonna hurt people.
I'm gonna hurt you.
You see, the press is
on their way here now.
And they're gonna witness
the awesome power of Sentry
as he takes down this ruthless group
of rogue agents,
thus beginning a new era
in which I decide how to keep
the American people safe,
answering to no one.
I'll be unimpeachable.
That's... never gonna happen.
Sentry, your first mission
is to take out these criminals.
I don't wanna hurt you guys.
Why don't you just turn yourselves in?
No, you don't wanna do this, Bobby.
You can call me The Sentry.
Please, don't do this.
You do not need to listen to her.
Robert, they don't think
you're good enough.
-That's not true.
-Remember?
You can trust me. I know you.
I don't think that you do.
Enough talking!
No one messes with
the West Chesapeake Valley Thunderbolts!
Thunderbolts?
Hey. No, no, no! No!
Wait!
Bob, no!
Alexei, wait!
Stop, Bob.
I'm so glad you were able to catch
a glimpse before your...
retirement.
Camera crews are assembling.
Finish the job, Robert.
Finish the job?
No.
What?
They're not a threat to me,
so why do I need to kill them?
You need to do what I say, Robert.
Why?
"Why"?
Okay. We need new plan.
Nah, no new plans.
That thing is just too powerful.
We just need to regroup and think.
-There's got to be a way to stop that guy.
-Oh, my God. We're not regrouping.
-This isn't even a team.
-Of course we're a team.
We are the Thunderbolts.
I don't know what that means.
It's her peewee soccer team thing. It's--
-We need to go somewhere to discuss this.
-Discuss what?
We are going to regroup.
We are going to go back in there.
-He turned my shield into a taco.
-He is a threat.
Oh, my God! Stop.
There is no "us." There is no "we."
Bob changed into that thing,
and there's nothing
any of you can do about it.
And what did you do exactly?
'Cause I seem to remember you getting
your arse beat way worse than mine.
Yeah. Yeah. I suck. I'm terrible.
We're all terrible.
Ava, you're not a hero.
You're not even a good person.
Bitch.
See?
Slow down. Um-nichka.
Alexei, I am not your um-nichka.
I haven't heard from you
or seen you in a year.
Okay, go easy on him.
-So you're nice now?
-Is it my turn?
No, you know you're a piece of trash,
Walker. So does your family.
Jesus.
We're all losers.
And we lost.
Yelena!
It needs to be more of a collaboration.
Like, the hair, for example. You know,
maybe I should have had more of a say.
Don't let those idiots get in your head.
The blond is great.
You sure? 'Cause, I don't know,
I thought I liked it.
Now I'm not so sure.
-Enough about the hair.
-Well, it's not just about the hair.
Well, you keep talking about the hair.
No, it's everything. My suit.
My name. My missions.
I mean...
why...
why would a god take orders
from anyone at all?
I think you're throwing around
the word "god" a bit loosely there.
No, no. Because you said
I was all-powerful, invincible,
and stronger than
a whole team of Avengers,
which includes at least one god, so...
But I'm starting to think maybe
you don't know what I am.
Goddamn it.
Or what I'm capable of.
Maybe I need to show you.
This is so irritating.
You were gonna turn on me,
just like the rest of them.
I'm not afraid of you, Robert.
It's not Robert you need to be afraid of.
Good girl.
You came to your senses.
Come here. Help me up.
I want a raise.
Okay, fine. Get cleanup on the body.
And tell Holt it's finally time
to go lethal on these losers.
Yelena!
-Little one.
-Go away.
No, I will not.
Well, then, chase me forever.
Fine, I will,
because that's what family does.
Oh, my God, stop.
If you cared, you would have called.
I would have heard from you.
I lost my sister again, but forever.
And you disappeared.
I'm sorry.
I don't know how to do this.
I'm not good at it.
I didn't think you wanted me.
I did.
I see that.
I'm late, but I'm... I'm here now.
Daddy, I'm so alone.
I don't have anything anymore.
All I do is sit and look at my phone
and think of all the terrible things
that I've done.
And then I go to work. And then I drink.
And then I come home to no one.
And I sit and I think
about all the terrible things I've done
-again and again.
-Yelena, stop. Stop.
-And I go crazy.
-We all have things that we regret.
No, but I have so many.
My first test at the Red Room.
Anya. She was just a child.
-She was so small.
-So were you.
I know.
I know there were dark times.
Very, very dark times.
But before, you were such
a special little girl.
Did you know this?
You walked into room.
You made it brighter.
You felt lot of joy.
I don't remember that feeling.
You were so kind.
Do you remember why you want to be goalie
on your terrible soccer team?
So I didn't have to run as much.
No.
Maybe that too, but you told me,
"I want to be the one everyone can rely on
if they make a mistake."
That Lena is still in you.
I still see her.
I don't.
You're stuck. You're alone.
You look only at the bad.
When I look at you,
I don't see your mistakes.
That's why we need each other.
Okay, that was really good.
-Val?
-Yeah?
It's cleanup from the penthouse,
and they're saying, well, there's no body.
What?
I don't know what I'm looking at up here.
It doesn't look good.
Aren't you tired of fighting?
Let me help you.
Holt, are you seeing this?
Is that...
Oh, no.
It's time.
Follow me!
Go, go! Go!
Dad!
Come on. You've got to... You've got to--
Mom?
You're safe, little one.
You all know the truth.
You can't outrun the emptiness.
I think Bob's dark side got superpowers.
-Get everybody off the street.
-Come on. Let's go. Let's go.
Come on! Come on! Go, go, go, go!
Everybody! Come on! Come on!
-Go, go, go!
-Go, go! Inside, inside!
Go, everyone, inside!
Let's go! Get in. Get in.
Yelena!
-Come on.
-Go, go, go!
Yelena, what are you doing?
It's what you said.
We're all alone.
All of us.
Wait!
Yelena!
-No, no, no! No! No, no!
-Hey, hey, hey. Come on.
Yelena!
Yelena, c'mon!
Lunch will be over soon.
Why'd you bring us so far out?
Anya, over here!
I'm sorry.
Bob!
Yelena!
No. No.
No, no, no!
No! No, no, no! No!
It's too late for that, friend.
Yelena!
Bob!
Bob! We don't have time for this.
Stop.
There you are.
-I'm going after her.
-And then what?
If she did that, she did it for a reason.
Well, what if she's dead, huh?
What if there's no coming back?
What if she isn't?
How do you know that?
No, wait, hold on.
I think she might have a point.
When I was back in the vault,
I saw something.
I went somewhere.
I can't explain it, but...
What did you see?
Enough, Bob.
Enough.
Yelena?
Hi.
Hey.
I just want to talk, okay?
About what?
About the stuff we spoke about
in the vault.
Hi.
What's up?
Not much. You know,
just watching New York disappear
into a big maze
of interconnected shame rooms.
You ever seen anything crazy
like that before?
I don't know what you want me to say.
That you'll stop.
It's not "me" me.
It's it.
The void.
I have these good days, you know?
Where I feel... I feel invincible.
But then there are a lot of bad days
when I remember that nothing...
nothing matters, you know?
So you're just gonna sit here
and let it take over?
Well, there's no use in fighting it.
At least I found a nice room.
The other rooms are much worse.
It is nice and quiet here, yeah.
What was that?
Disrespected in my own house!
Don't mind them. It'll be over soon.
Say it again! Say it again!
-I shouldn't have. I'm sorry.
-Again.
Don't touch her.
Big man speaks up.
-Bob, shut your mouth.
-Mom, no.
My son, the hero. Look at you.
-What are you gonna do? You a hero, Bobby?
-Bob. Sit down.
Sit down. You're making it worse.
You always made it worse.
I'm sorry.
No, it's fine.
What I said to you before was wrong, Bob.
You can't stuff it down.
You can't hold it in all alone.
No one can.
We have to let it out.
We have to spend time together.
And even if it doesn't
make the emptiness go away,
I promise you it will feel lighter.
How do you know?
Because it already has for me.
We can find a way out of here together.
Will you try and leave here with me?
Okay.
Look out!
Who's doing this, Bob?
I think I am.
Just try to get used to it, okay?
There's no death here.
The pain only gets worse.
Evil pillow!
Lena.
You came for us.
What did you see? Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I have a great past, so I'm totally fine.
Yeah, this place is messed up.
We're here together.
That's what matters.
Thank you, guys. Really.
Of course.
Here we are,
Shane's Elite Electronic Thunderbolts.
It's not Shane's.
Okay, okay.
Just how do we get out of here?
I mean, as far as I know,
it's just endless rooms.
Wait, you said that this was
the nicest room you found
and the others are way worse, right?
Yeah.
Okay, well, show us the worst.
Where do you think you're going, Robert?
Well, he seems nice.
The strangest mission
I've ever been part of.
-This way!
-Go, go, go!
Come on!
Oh, no.
Bob, you hit me with
that sign one more time--
I was on meth!
This way!
Come on. Come on. Go.
I've been here before.
This is where it started.
I was roaming around Southeast Asia,
thought I'd figure something out,
or at least find more drugs.
Then there was this guy,
started talking to me
about a medical study.
A trial drug that could make me stronger.
Felt like a miracle.
I'd finally get to show everyone
that I was more.
That I was…
something.
And look what you unleashed.
The most shameful thing of all was
thinking you could be anything more than
nothing.
We're leaving.
No.
Stop.
Just… let them go.
Wait. You think they care about you?
You don't matter.
To anyone.
That's not true.
No!
Don't hurt her.
Robert, the hero.
I'm stronger than you.
Let's see.
Get up, Bobby.
You thought you were
gonna be some great man?
Some savior?
You can't even save yourself.
We will always be alone.
Is that all you've got?
This isn't right.
Bob, stop!
This is what he wants!
I'm here.
It will always be just us.
I'm here. You are not alone.
Come on.
Sweetie.
You were great in there, Bob.
Thanks, Walker.
Hey, wait, in where?
What happened here?
Sorry, I'm just a little fuzzy.
Okay. Are you serious?
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Yes. I need an extraction right now.
What? No. I don't have backup.
I need help.
I'm going to kill that person.
Okay. Wait, wait, wait. Hold on.
What happens when he regains his memory?
-Okay. Come on.
-Me too?
Yep. We stick together from now on.
That's nice.
Can't kill her. We gotta take her in.
Can't kill her.
Maybe when we take her in,
I break a few bones.
I'd like to kill her.
Maybe when he does get his memory back,
he can fix this stupid thing.
-At least let me break her legs.
-Okay, guys.
Then you can drag her.
I know we're all having
a lot of feelings right now.
-I am too. I get it.
-Hi.
Give me half-- half a second.
Are we live?
Great.
For years, I have been working secretly
to develop a new age of protection.
Today, the citizens of
the United States needed that protection.
And thanks to my hard work, they got it.
Ladies and gentlemen…
meet…
the new Avengers.
We own you now.
So many choices, huh?
Hard to decide.
Oh, look, Wheaties. Wow.
With its toasted wholewheat flakes,
wholegrain, vitamins.
Give you energy. Good for kids, huh?
Okay.
Thanks.
You're welcome.
That's me on the box.
But we are the Avengers.
The government said so.
How does Sam Wilson not understand that?
Well, he does have the shield.
-Well, I got a shield too.
-It's not a shield.
-Yeah, it is a shield.
-It's a shitty shield.
It's a great shield, Bucky.
Okay, if he puts together a team,
and then the team is called the Avengers,
who are the real Avengers?
Well, that's the question
the Internet has been asking,
and judging by the very nasty memes
that I've read,
they don't think that it's us.
-Weren't you going to talk to him?
-I already did.
-And?
-It went poorly.
I don't know what any of these buttons do.
It's unbelievable
they didn't mark any of them.
You know he's filed
for copyright of the name?
-Did he?
-We're losing credibility.
Which we had very little to begin with.
And now there's this huge space crisis,
and no one's telling us about it.
We're running out of space already?
It's impossible.
This building is enormous.
-What?
-Outer space.
Outer space.
Run a threat analysis.
I want a full report.
Running threat analysis.
Hello, team.
The hell are you wearing?
I heard about Sam Wilson.
He's dumb, litigious man, but I am smart.
I am smart man. I have smart solve.
Avengerz.
With a 'Z,' there is no copyright.
-No.
-So soft too.
Feel like bottom of baby seal.
You want to… you want to savor that?
I don't want to touch your baby seal butt.
-I have one for you.
-I don't want it.
I have one for you. I got you one.
I got you one.
And for you, Bob, in the corner hiding,
pretending to read the book.
We're all matching.
All part of super team!
-Unidentified craft entering orbit.
-You should get a satellite image.
-Get a satellite image.
-And fire up--
And fire… I was gonna say that.
And fire up the jets.
We wouldn't need to fire up the jets
if we had a Sentry who could fly.
I know… Sorry. Sorry, guys.
Can't be the Sentry without the,
you know, other side.
I did the dishes though.
And what are we gonna do
just, like, ride Bob into the sky?
Yes. Can you imagine Red Guardian
riding on top of Sentry,
cresting over the clouds?
This is why we are Avengers with a 'Z.'
Satellite image populating.
Extradimensional ship entering atmosphere.
Extradimensional? What does that mean?
It's a… it's a cool ship.